<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SmartHR FanControl</string>

    <string name="info_supported_devices_title">Supported Devices</string>
    <string name="info_supported_devices_content"><![CDATA[
        The app is designed to be compatible with a range of Xiaomi Smart Fans. The following models should be supported:<br/><br/>
        • Pedestal Fan P9<br/>
        • Pedestal Fan P10<br/>
        • Mija Pedestal Fan<br/>
        • Pedestal Fan P15<br/>
        • Mi Smart Standing Fan 2<br/>
        • Mi Smart Standing Fan 2 Pro<br/><br/>
        <b>Please Note:</b> While the app is designed to work with all the models listed above, it has only been physically tested on the <b>Mi Smart Standing Fan 2 Pro</b>. Functionality with other models is based on the protocol implementation from the \'python-miio\' library and is not guaranteed.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="info_instructions_title">Instructions</string>
    <string name="info_instructions_content"><![CDATA[
        Welcome to SmartHR FanControl! This guide will help you set up the app in a few simple steps.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 1: Obtain Fan IP Address and Token</b><br/>
        To control your Xiaomi fan, the app needs its local IP address and a unique 32-character token. A highly recommended tool for this is the "Xiaomi Cloud Tokens Extractor". You can find it by searching online or visiting its GitHub page.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2: Configure the Fan in the App</b><br/>
        1. Navigate to the <b>Settings</b> tab.<br/>
        2. In "Fan Config", enter the IP and Token.<br/>
        3. Tap <b>SAVE FAN SETTINGS</b>.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3: Pair Your Heart Rate Sensor</b><br/>
        1. Navigate to the <b>HR Sensors</b> tab.<br/>
        2. Tap <b>SEARCH HEART RATE SENSORS</b>.<br/>
        3. Tap <b>Pair</b> on a detected device, then <b>Select</b> it from the paired list.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4: Configure Auto Mode (Optional)</b><br/>
        In <b>Settings -> Auto Mode</b>, you can customize the HR-to-speed curve. Tap the (i) icon for details on each setting. Remember to tap <b>SAVE AUTO MODE SETTINGS</b>.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5: Start Controlling!</b><br/>
        1. On the <b>Main</b> screen, turn the fan on using the <b>FAN ON</b> button.<br/>
        2. Toggle the <b>Auto Mode</b> switch to enable automatic control.<br/><br/>
        Enjoy your workout!<br/><br/>
        <b>Visual Guide with Screenshots</b><br/>
        For a more detailed guide with screenshots, please visit the project\'s <a href="https://github.com/chudzik28/SmartHR-FanControl">official GitHub Page</a>.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="info_privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="info_privacy_policy_content"><![CDATA[
        Last updated: October 30, 2025<br/><br/>
        <b>1. Data Collection and Use</b><br/>
        This application is a hobby project and does not collect, store, or transmit any personal data. It does not contain advertisements or analytics.<br/><br/>
        <b>2. Data Storage and Security</b><br/>
        All settings (fan IP/token, device addresses) are stored exclusively and encrypted on your device. No data ever leaves your phone.<br/><br/>
        <b>3. Heart Rate (Biometric) Data</b><br/>
        Heart rate data is processed in real-time on your device and is never stored. Enabling the "Heart Rate Sharing" feature is your choice and responsibility.<br/><br/>
        <b>4. Permissions</b><br/>
        Permissions are used exclusively for the app\'s core functionality (communicating with your devices).<br/><br/>
        <b>5. Third-Party Services</b><br/>
        The "Buy Me a Coffee" link redirects to a third-party website, governed by its own privacy policy.<br/><br/>
        <b>6. Changes to This Privacy Policy</b><br/>
        We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the new policy within the application.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="info_terms_of_use_title">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="info_terms_of_use_content"><![CDATA[
        Last updated: October 30, 2025<br/><br/>
        By downloading or using this application ("App"), you agree to be bound by these Terms of Use.<br/><br/>
        <b>1. Software License</b><br/>
        This App is free software, distributed under the terms of the <b>GNU General Public License v3.0 (GPLv3)</b>. The full license text governs your rights to use, modify, and distribute this software.<br/><br/>
        <b>2. "As Is" Basis and Limitation of Liability</b><br/>
        This App is a hobby project provided "AS IS" without any warranties. In no event shall the developer be liable for any damages resulting from the use of the App.<br/><br/>
        <b>3. Disclaimer of Affiliation</b><br/>
        This App is an independent project and is not affiliated with, or endorsed by, Xiaomi Inc.<br/><br/>
        <b>4. User Responsibility</b><br/>
        You are solely responsible for obtaining your fan\'s IP address and token and for all consequences of using this App.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="info_oss_licenses_title">Open Source Licenses</string>
    <string name="info_oss_licenses_summary">View licenses of open source software used in this app.</string>

    <string name="info_acknowledgements_title">Acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="info_acknowledgements_content"><![CDATA[
        The core fan control logic in this application is a Kotlin reimplementation of the excellent work done by the developers of the open-source <b>\'python-miio\'</b> library, which is licensed under the GNU General Public License v3.0. This project would not have been possible without their efforts.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="info_gpl_license_title">GNU GPL v3.0 License</string>
    <string name="info_gpl_license_content"><![CDATA[
        This program is free software, distributed under the terms of the GNU General Public License v3.0.<br/><br/>
        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY. See the full license for more details.<br/><br/>
        <b>Source Code</b><br/>
        The complete source code for this application is available at:<br/>
        <a href="https://github.com/chudzik28/SmartHR-FanControl">https://github.com/chudzik28/SmartHR-FanControl</a><br/><br/>
        <b>Full License Text</b><br/>
        View the full license at:<br/>
        <a href="https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.html">https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.html</a>
    ]]></string>
</resources>